你在干嘛呢
uh, what's happening right now?
麦克斯 你在吸毒吗
Max, are you smoking crack?
这不是毒品 是唇膏
it's not crack, it's lipstick.
毒品我倒买得起
I can afford crack.
我的好唇膏快要用完了 没钱买新的
I'm at the end of my good lipstick and I can't afford
只好学《绝命毒师》 烧一烧炼一炼
to buy a new one so I'm going all Breaking Bad.
《绝命毒师》
"Breaking Bad"?
我们更像是"没命毒虱"[又穷又苦]吧
We're more like broke and sad.
你在加热提炼唇膏 看我
You're freebasing lipstick and look,
这只高跟鞋都摇摇欲断了
this heel is starting to wobble.
来 塞进去 撑住
here, stick this in and hold it.
我发誓这种话我以前说过
I swear I've said that before,
不过肯定跟鞋子无关
but I don't think it was about shoes.
美人 都过了十分钟了
yo, dollface. It's been ten minutes!
他的杂烩浓汤 我的意大利面
His chowder, my spaghetti.
在哪里
Where's the food?
"在哪里"
"Where's the food"?
你怎么不问问 你脖子在哪里
Where's your neck?
老子根本没再听 我在看你的奶子呢
I wasn't listening. I was looking at your boobs.
我会尽我所能
well, I do what I can
不过老娘胸再大 也没你的男人奶大
but they'll never be as big as yours.
上菜 肉丸
Pick up. Meatball.
喂 辣妹 你们的热菜呢
Hey, hot stuff. Where's the hot stuff?
麦克斯 你做得对
Oh, Max. You were right.
这只高跟鞋比以前更...不对
This heel is much more--no.
不 等等 别这样
No, wait! No, it's not.
这会...
It's gonna--
这两男的在打类固醇长肌肉后
Those are the biggest balls those guys have had
双腿间第一次有这么大的"肉丸"呢
in their laps since they started steroids.
真不敢相信你用胶带把鞋和脚包在一起
I can't believe you masking taped the shoe to your leg.
我知道 但这双可是名牌鞋
I know but these are Christian Louboutins and
即使被包得面目全非 经典的红鞋底
even all busted up like this they still have
还是能显而易见
the classic red bottoms.
你知道什么还是红的吗
You know what else has red bottoms?
狒狒屁股
Baboons.
如果你能脚踏两只狒狒
Walk around with a couple of them on your feet
再下一定钦佩不已
and I'm impressed.
至少现在看不见那些白痴蝴蝶结了
Well, at least now you can't see those stupid bows.
谁会在鞋子上装蝴蝶结啊
Who put bows on their shoes?
内装什么礼物啊 你的臭脚吗
What's the gift? Your stinky feet?
你以为我喜欢这些蝴蝶结啊
You don't think I hate the bows?
我一年前纯粹是一时冲动才买这双鞋
I bought these as an impulse purchase over a year ago.
鬼知道我要套着它们一辈子啊
I didn't know I'd be shackled with them for eternity.
卡洛琳
Oh, Caroline.
我从来没注意你有一只畸形足
I never noticed you had a club foot.
不然我就帮你跟我兄弟牵红线了
I would have set you up with my brother.
我在餐馆把鞋子弄坏了
I broke my shoe in the diner.
我来帮你吧
Oh, I can help.
我总是随身装着我的运动鞋
I always carry my gym shoes in my bag.
抱歉款式有点过于保守
I'm sorry they're so conservative
不过举重房里基佬真的很多嘛
but the weight room is a real meat rack.
苏菲 你真好
Sophie, that's so sweet of you.
但我还有一双备用的鞋子可以穿
But I still have one pair of my own shoes to wear.
你拿着吧 有备无患嘛
Oh, well take them just in case.
你最好还是拿着吧
You should take them.
没准上班路上 能挣个20块"站街费"呢
You'll make $20 just walking to work.
你的信跟我的混在一起了
And some of your mail got mixed in with mine.
那个邮差大姐已经搞错三次了
This is like the third time that mail lady did that.
好啦 晚安咯
All right. Nighty night.
麦克斯 你不会相信是谁寄信来了
Max, you will not believe what just came addressed to you.
我先解释下 我不是山达基教徒
Let me explain. I'm not a Scientologist.
我只去过那一次 因为我听说
I just went that one time because I heard
有个有钱人在征婚[教中仪式]
some rich guy was looking for a wife.
不是啦 我们申请的信用卡被预先核准了
No, we've been pre-approved for a credit card.
什么 我们怎么会被预先核准呢
What? How the hell did we get pre-approved?
上面说我们只要上网申请
It says all we have to do is go online and apply
两分钟内就能获批
and we can be approved in under two minutes.
别着急 钟楼怪人
Slow down, Quasimodo.
我不能有信用卡
I can't have a credit card.
有人给了我一包趣多多饼干
Someone gave me a bag of chips Ahoy cookies once
我一口气全吃光了
And I ate the entire thing without breathing.
你又不是小孩子了
Well, you're not a child anymore.
你有自控能力
You have more discipline.
这是昨天的事
The cookies were yesterday.
那是什么 那个旋转的轮子是什么意思
Okay, what is that thing? What is that spinning wheel?
那是在处理我们的申请
It's just processing our application.
不 不是的
No, it's not.
它是在查出我们的一切
It's finding out everything about us.
这一秒它查出你父亲偷了数百万美元
Now it's finding out your dad stole millions of dollars.
这一秒它查出我被八家DQ冰淇淋店解雇过
Now it's finding out I got fired from eight Dairy Queens.
这一秒它查出我被八家DQ店解雇的原因
Now it's finding out why I got fired from eight dairy queens.
天啊 麦克斯 我们通过了
Oh, my god. Max, we're approved.
我们的申请通过了
We've just been approved.
搞毛啊 他们有病吗
What? What is wrong with them?
难道DQ店毛都没举报吗
Does dairy queen report nothing?
重新回去查 拒绝我们的申请
Get back on there and disapprove us.
好了 冷静
Okay. Calm down.
为了事业 我们需要这张卡
We need this card for our business.
我们只需如实与对方沟通
All we have to do is communicate with each other
每一笔花销就行了
about every purchase, you know?
开诚布公
Keep an open dialogue.
所以 开诚布公地说
So, opening dialogue.
出于商业需要 我要买双美鞋
For our business,I would like a pair of Louboutins.
开诚布公地说 不行
Opening dialogue. No.
这种模仿哑剧的对话蠢爆了 我讨厌艺术
And I felt stupid miming that. I hate the arts.
你不能想要什么 就买什么
Look, you can't get everything you want.
我还想要一盒子蜥蜴呢
I would like a box of lizards.
我一直很喜欢蜥蜴
Love lizards, always have,
但我也没有要用信用卡买啊
but you don't see me putting that on a credit card.
我是为了商业洽谈才买新鞋子的
I need a new pair of shoes for business meetings.
俗话说得好
You know what they say,
"佛要金装 人要衣装"
"Dress for the job you want, not the job you have".
好吧
Okay, fine.
如果你要买美鞋 那我也要买
If you're getting the shoes, then I'm getting what I want.
希望你不会介意
I hope you're happy with an apartment
一屋子全是蜥蜴和唇膏
full of lizards and lipstick.
并且还会有涂着唇膏的蜥蜴哟
Also, some of those lizards will be wearing lipstick.
厄尔 你今晚看着特别帅气呀
Earl, you are looking particularly gorgeous this evening.
我本来要说"少奉承我" 但确实
Well, I would say, "don't flatter me" but let's face it.
今晚一切都无懈可击
Everything came together tonight.
又换了个妞吗 我是不是应该满腔怒火呀
Is it another woman? Should I be filled with anger?
比我平时更凶点吗
I mean, more than I usually am?
我只想在我儿子来的时候 看起来体面点
I just want to look nice for my son when he comes in.
不是吧 我要见你的孩子了吗
What? No way, I'm going to meet your kid?
其中之一而已
Well, one of them.
"其中之一" 你有几个孩子呀
"One of them"? How many do you have?
目前为止吗
So far?
厄尔 我真是爱死你了
Oh, Earl, I love you.
是我的儿子达瑞斯
This is my son, Darius.
他是全底特律的是克莱斯勒头号销售员
He's the number one Chrysler salesman in all of Detroit,
如果我没记错他的话
and he's my very favorite,
他是我最喜欢的一个儿子了
if he's the one I'm thinking of.
抱歉 请问您是
Excuse me, but aren't you Max
麦克斯自制小蛋糕的麦克斯吗
Of Max's homemade cupcakes?
厄尔 瞧瞧
Earl, look.
今天我们的信用卡寄过来了
Our credit card came in the mail today.
看见没 "麦克斯·布莱克"
See? "Max black".
可以挥别我在六旗乐园捡到的卡了
No more using the card I found at Six Flags.
感谢你从不查看结算单 艾格尼丝·琴
Thank you for never checking your statement, Agnes Chin.
姑娘们 听我一句
Girls, take my advice
要慎用那玩意
and be very careful with that thing.
信用卡比
Credit cards are more trouble
在儿童演唱会出没的牧师还可怕
than a priest at a Wiggles concert.
收到 厄尔
Yes, Earl.
真是难以置信 我们事业专用的信用卡
I can't believe it. A credit card for our business.
那我们什么时候去买鞋子和蜥蜴呀
So when are we getting the shoes and lizards?
麦克斯 记住
Max, remember.
我们得用成熟的心态去对待
We have to be grown-ups about this.
当然
Of course.
"来两只蜥蜴 不 来三只好了"
"Two lizards, please. No, make it three."
你好 我是来找厄尔的
Hi, I'm looking for Earl.
不 我不是来还过期大麻的
And no, I'm not here to return a bag of skunky weed.
天啊 见到你非常激动
Oh, my god. I'm so excited to see you.
来进来 我会好好招待你的
Come on in, I'll take really, really good care of you.
告诉你 我刚跟我老婆分居
Oh, you need to know I just separated from my wife,
所以我可是有点脆弱哦
so I'm a little vulnerable.
她一般不对顾客这么好
She's not usually this nice to customers.
她只是太激动了
She's just excited.
因为她要买蜥蜴啦
She's about to come into some lizards.
再重申一遍
Yeah, again.
我重回泡妞战场有一段时日了
I've been out the dating pool for a while,
所以一切对我来说 都是性暗示哦
so everything sound like a sexual innuendo to me.
他不是顾客 你仔细看看
He is not a customer. Look at him.
你不觉得像谁吗
Don't you see the resemblance?
天啊 敢情他是你父亲吗
Oh, my God is he your father?
是啊 他是我爸
Yes. He's my father.
然后我妈是一根粉笔
And my mother is a piece of chalk.
老爹
Daddy!
谢天谢地 就是我想的那一个
Thank god, it is the one I thought.
我的乖孩子哟
There's my little boy!
达瑞斯 厄尔是个什么样的爸爸
So, Darius, what was Earl like as a dad?
感觉一定很棒吧
It must have been great, huh?
我敢说他一定给你准备最酷的午餐
I bet he packed the coolest lunches.
还给大麻让你休息时间抽 一盒琴酒混果汁
A joint for recess, and a gin and juice box.
对啊 他是个很棒的爸爸
Oh, yeah, yeah. He was a great dad.
我是说 他一直陪在我身边
I mean, he was always there.
童年时期之外啦
Except for my childhood.
这不笑不行啊
You've gotta laugh!
厄尔就坐在你旁边呢
Earl is sitting right there.
说笑而已嘛 别太较真了 小不点
Well, it's a joke. Take it easy there, fun size.
阿憨 别生气
Han, take no offense.
他只是跟你开个小玩笑
He's just pulling your leg a little.
达瑞斯一直很搞笑
Darius has always been funny.
为什么我会想起特伦斯呢
Why am I thinking about Terrence?
不知道 我才是搞笑那个 爸
I don't know. I'm the funny one, dad.
我不记得我们家有人叫特伦斯啊
I don't recall there being a Terrence in our family,
不过 我哪知道你的"种"播了多远呀
But then again, I don't know how far you've thrown your seed.
这不笑不行啊
You've gotta laugh.
是咩
Do you?
达瑞斯被克莱斯勒代理商
Darius was voted the funniest salesman
选为最搞笑的销售员
at the Chrysler dealership.
没错 所以我辞了我的工作
Yes, I was. And that's why I quit my job.
去追求梦想 当一名单口相声员
To pursue my dream to become a comedian.
看见没 他好好笑
See? See, he's funny.
一直在开玩笑
Always making jokes.
那不是玩笑 老爹
That's not a joke, daddy.
真的不是 我进城
No, no, that's why I'm in town.
就是为了明天晚上喜剧俱乐部的面试
To audition at the comedy club tomorrow night.
我已经想好我的艺名了
I already got my stage name.
"笑星达叔"
"Darius the hilarious".
名字超有才的 对不对
I think it's a good choice, right?
是咩
Is it?
放心吧 达哥
Well, obviously, big D,
我们都会到场支持你的
we will all be there to support you.
是咩
Will we?
慢着 达瑞斯 这事是怎么搞的
hold up, Darius. How did all of this happen?
我认识一个卖卡迪拉克的家伙
Well, I mean, I knew a guy at Cadillac
他认识个卖丰田的 那人又认识卖斯巴鲁的
who knew a guy at Toyota who knew a guy at Subaru
卖斯巴鲁的卖了一辆道奇车给俱乐部老板
who sold the club owner a dodge.
然后老板开着道奇车撞了个小孩
And then he hit a kid with it.
那孩子应该闪开"道"的
The kid should have dodged.
这很好笑吧
You gotta laugh!
有小孩死了呢 这事还笑得出来吗
There's a dead kid in the mix and we got to laugh?
他没幽默感不是他的错
It's not his fault he's not funny.
我们把他的幽默感放到一个很高的架子上
We put his sense of humor on a high shelf.
麦克斯
Hey, Max, you know,
老爹总是对我说你很特别
daddy always told me you were special,
现在我见识到了
and now I see it.
不仅仅是很捧场我的笑话
And it's not just because you think everything I say is funny.
-你有家人的感觉 -是吗
- You feel like family. - I do?
我一直想要个大哥
Oh, I always wanted a brother...
大哥级的大哥
who was a brother.
麦克斯 你是想我今晚一个人招待所有人吗
Max, do you expect me to wait on all the tables tonight?
拜托 我现在有点忙
well, I am kind of in the middle of
忙着一家团聚
my family reunion right now.
笑星先生的汤呢
And where is Mr. Hilarious' soup?
瞧这位金发妞 她一定在想
Look at blondie, here. She's like,
"老天啊 黑人也喝汤的吗"
"Oh my God, do black people even eat soup?"
"随便啦"
"It's like, whatever."
后面这句超级像卡洛琳的
That is a dead-on Caroline.
是咩
Is it?
这是你今晚的点菜单
Here is your order ticket from tonight.
这叠是发现食物里有头发的食客账单
This pile is for the people who found hair.
这些是食客们发现的头发
These are the hairs that the people found.
你的口音像俄国人
Oh, you sound russian.
真讽刺 那你还不赶紧[与俄国人音似]去做汤
That's funny because you're not rushin' to make my soup.
不 不 我在开玩笑呢
No, no, no, no. I'm kidding you, man.
我懂 你在后台太忙了
I get it. You're just too busy back there
忙着不擦除臭剂
not putting on deodorant.
这很好笑吧
You gotta laugh.
是咩
Do you?
麦克斯 可能是我神经敏感
Max, I might be crazy but now I feel like
但我觉得这鞋又要...
the heel of this shoe's starting to--
惨了 我得去擦一擦
Oh, gosh. Now I got to go wipe this down.
我明天本来打算穿这件去面试呢
You know, I was going to wear this for my audition.
-只许成功不许失败 -是啊
- And that's gotta go well. - Yes, it does.
是啊 儿子 底特律就两种工作
Because son, there are two jobs in Detroit,
而其中一种你还不干了
and you just quit one of them.
老爹 别担心 我会让你以我为荣
Don't worry, daddy. I'll make you proud.
看到成果你就知道了
All right? You'll see.
老爹也不是没判断错误过
Daddy's been wrong before.
他当年也觉得我上不了《灵魂列车》
He didn't think I could make it on Soul Train,
我也上了啊
But there I was,
节目上左下角的小角落露了脸
in the bottom left corner on Soul Train.
我好过意不去
I feel so terrible.
我们肯定是得给人家买件新的啦
Well, you know we have to buy him a new shirt.
麦克斯 我今晚才赚了七块
Max, I've made seven dollars so far.
我们哪买得起啊
We can't afford to buy him a shirt.
可以买件价钱过得去的衣服嘛
We can go shopping for a reasonable shirt.
他也算自己人 这是应该的
We have to. He's family.
是咩
Is he?
但我真不喜欢他那种嘲笑人的幽默
And I have to say, I don't like that brand of put-down humor.
他那对金发妞刻板印象的嘲笑
And that blonde stereotype?
我什么时候说过"随便啦"这词了
I mean, I don't even say "Whatever".
算了 无所谓 随便啦
But, you know, it's fine. Whatever.
麦克斯 慢点
Max, slow down.
穿着苏菲的大号"运动鞋" 我走不快
I can't walk any faster in Sophie's giant sneakers.
她居然能穿着这玩意举250磅重的哑铃
I can't believe she benches 250 in these.
我的老天啊
Oh, my God.
我的手摸到了地铁站的地板
My hand just touched the subway floor.
怎么才能知道这块地还没被人尿过呢
How do I know someone didn't pee here?
宝贝别紧张 我在这尿过
Oh, honey, I've peed here.
纽约不就是尿尿之城嘛
This is New York. It's made of pee.
满手沾尿就是你不穿平底鞋的报应
And pee hand is what you get for refusing to wear flat shoes.
想都别想
No way.
住的地方离下水道已经够接近
I'm living so close to the gutter as it is.
再矮下去还得了
I can't risk being any shorter.
我们就跟达叔约在这里
Here's where we're meeting Darius.
"最炫地铁风"
"Subway style".
每次我经过这个地方 我都在想
Every time I walk by this place I wonder
谁会买这里的衣服啊
"who would ever shop here?"
原来就是我们这种人
Now I know -- us.
首先我的鞋跟断了
First my heel breaks,
然后还在地下的商店采购
and now I'm shopping underground.
我的人生低谷还能更低吗
How much lower can I get?
低到得在地核吃早午餐吗
Brunch on the earth's core?
原谅我还在一边吃东西
Oh. Excuse my mouthful.
没想到会有女士来
Mm, I wasn't expecting ladies.
通常都是皮条客跟牧师来这逛
We usually just sell to pimps and pastors.
有何能为两位美女效劳的吗
What can I help you dolls with?
我们是来跟朋友碰面的
Actually, we're just here meeting a friend.
来帮忙他选衣服
We're going to help him pick out a shirt.
那位男士啊
Oh, that guy?
他已经在试衣间试衣服了
He's already in the dressing room trying one on now.
先告诉你们 如果嫌太贵
Now, listen, if the price is too high,
你可以跟我来"讲讲价"
you and I can, uh, negotiate.
你也行啦
Or you.
我不敢相信我们要用辛苦赚的小费
I still can't believe we're using our tip money
来给他买新衣服
to buy him a shirt.
估计也就花个40块钱嘛
We're only going to spend like $40.
而且人家也说了 你头"下去"
And you heard the man. It can go down.
价钱就跟着下去
if you go down.
女士们 你们来啦
Oh, hey ladies. There you are.
你们看 我改穿高调一点
Look, I switched it up a little bit.
我穿粉红色好看吗
Do you like me in pink?
我的基男友觉得好看
My boyfriend does.
让我俏脸泛红 屁股发红
He says it makes my cheeks look rosy, all four of them.
这不笑不行啊 这不笑不行啊
You gotta laugh, you gotta laugh!
达叔 我们当你自己人
Darius, we're family,
所以我要跟你说实话
so I'm just going to tell you like it is.
你这段子有点太过了
That material feels a little funky.
你在丰田汽车遇见的人能接受
I mean, that kind of humor might have worked over at Toyota--
-我是在克莱斯勒 -随便啦
- It's Chrysler. - Whatever.
但你现在来到了纽约
But this is New York.
这里有很多的同性恋 或者金发人士
there are a lot of people, be them gays, or blondes,
可能听了会不舒服
who might take offense to that.
我个人没意见 但随便啦
I mean, I don't, but, whatever.
没事没事 那些只是闹着说
Oh, no, no, no. I was just playing.
我今晚的演出不会说那些段子
That's not the kind of stuff I'm gonna do in my act tonight.
我在家乡时 跟另一个说相声的
No, I wrote some real jokes with a comic back home.
一起编了不少段子 他是犹太人 绝对"好笑"
and, he's Jewish, so you know it's gonna be funny.
他也绝对"不小气"
And not cheap.
又来了 你看 就是这类的...
Again, see? That's the kind of stuff...
卡洛琳 大家就爱听重口过火的
Caroline, come on. It's so wrong it's right.
这些是我今晚要讲的段子
Look, I have the jokes right here.
先让你们"试驾"一下 看看反应如何
Let's take them on a little test drive and see how they do.
来吧 站后退点哦 女士们
All right? So back it up, ladies.
留一点让你们笑倒打滚的空间
You going to need some laughing room.
肯定会很好笑吧
this is going to be hilarious.
在场有人开斯玛特吗
Anybody here have a smart car?
开"半台车"在街上溜达 车主肯定不聪明
Because I don't think it's smart to drive half a car.
你们这反应... 我再琢磨琢磨好了
That was new, I'll keep working on it.
好啦 再说一个
All right, let's try another one.
我知道了 可能是站得不够远
You know what, maybe we weren't back far enough.
这就对了
Yeah!
站过来就感到笑气逼人了 对吧 卡洛琳
Yeah, that feels funnier already, right Caroline?
好的
All right.
你们知道什么人不开斯玛特吗
You know who doesn't drive a smart car?
聪明人 他们没这么笨
Smart people. They don't do it.
这不笑不行啊
You gotta laugh.
真的该笑了啊
Seriously.
必须得笑 我把宝都押在这上面了
You've got to. I've got a lot riding on this.
我懂你笑点了
I just got it.
老天爷啊 他冷爆了
Oh, my God. He stinks.
比冰块还冷啊 达叔今晚要出糗了
He stinks on ice. Darius is gonna bomb tonight
更惨的是 他会在厄尔面前出糗
And worse, he's going to bomb in front of Earl.
厄尔最引以为傲的儿子就是达叔了
And Earl's pretty sure that's the son he's most proud of.
你说得对 那怎么办
You're right. What are we gonna do?
我知道两位小姐是来挑衬衫的
Now I know you lovely ladies came in for a shirt,
请容在下给你们推荐这西装外套吧
but can I interest you in a nice suit?
瞧这件 多经典
Look at this one. It's a classic.
地面上开的店可不卖这颜色哦
You can't get this color above ground.
就是这个 达叔需要一套西装
That's it. Darius needs a suit.
专业的单口相声员都穿西装
All the professional comedians wear suits,
而且你也说了
and like you said,
做什么工
you have to dress for the job you want.
而他的烂段子
And with jokes like that,
得靠最搞笑的西装才能救
he needs the funniest suit they have.
你们有辛巴达系列的西装吗
Do you have anything from the Sinbad collection?
有的
I do.
麦克斯 光靠搞笑西装救不起吧
Max, I don't think the suit's gonna be enough.
我觉得还得再加点东西
I think he needs something else,
比如搭配一个布偶
you know, like, a puppet.
布偶吗
A puppet?
够蠢够好笑 就是这个了
That's exactly what he needs.
我昨晚跟个男人出去约会
I went out with a guy last night.
他问我能不能各付各的[荷兰式]
Asked me if we could go dutch.
我说 "不知道呢
I said, "I don't know."
我不会说荷兰语的你个小气废柴"
"what's Dutch for cheap-ass bitch?"
把他一脚踹飞啦
You kick him to the curb!
稍后继续
We'll be right back,
老娘要先去休息了
because mama's gotta go put her feet up.
小姐
Uh, miss?
等你忙完了能给我们再上一轮酒吗
Can we get another round when you get a chance?
再一轮吗
Another round?
我们没喝到瞎了之前 酒都别停
And keep them coming until we can no longer see.
都算我卡上吧
Put it on my card.
没问题
You got it.
这句话 怎么说都还是爽
Man, that feels good every time.
麦克斯 别以为
Hey, Max. Just because
你请我喝酒
you're buying me drinks
我就会无节操的对你投怀送抱
doesn't mean I'm going to put out.
这根芹菜就是我在相声社的麦克风
My celery stick is my microphone at the comedy club!
我来了 我来了
I'm here, I'm here.
有买到布偶吗
Did you get the puppet?
姐出马 当然是办妥了
Oh, I've got the puppet.
请进
Hey, come on in.
姑娘们 你们好吗
Hey, girls. How you doing?
笑星达叔打了鸡血了呢
Darius the hilarious is pumped.
状态超好 准备笑力全开
I'm totally in my zone right now.
配这西装 笑死人不偿命啊
And I can't miss in this suit.
这个嘛...
Well...
达叔 我们就是来跟你谈这事的
Darius, that's what we wanted to talk to you about.
-我们都是你的支持者 -铁杆粉丝
- You know we're big fans. - Big, big fans.
你人超好 段子超好笑
You're amazing, your act's incredible.
传说中的笑星达叔
you are Darius the hilarious.
我们都爱你的斯玛特段子
Max and I love the smart car stuff.
笑星之名 绝非虚传
It's hilarious, per your name.
但在纽约这小破村
But, well, it is New York.
很多人不聪明 也没车
not a lot of people are smart, or have cars.
纽约嘛 你懂得
Yeah, you know New York.
完全不在时尚的尖端
not exactly the cutting edge.
下午跟你分开之后 我们俩有了个主意
So, after Max and I left you, we had a thought.
我们给你买了个布偶
We got you a puppet.
没错 我是有点喝高了
And, yes, I was stoned.
但卡洛琳看了也笑个不停哦
But Caroline was laughing just as hard as me.
你们买了什么给我
You got me a what?
布偶 买了个布偶给你
A puppet. We got you a puppet.
我从不用布偶的啊
But I don't use a puppet.
用过一次就知道啦
Until you do.
想象一下 你说完个段子
Just imagine, at the end of your act
-或段子开头 -甚至是整个段子中
- or in the beginning... - Or all the way through.
先生女士们 笑星达叔
Ladies and gentlemen, Darius the hilarious
与他的搭档 贾斯汀·逼勃
and his partner, Justin Beaver!
"哇靠 女孩 哇靠啊[水坝]"
"Damn, girl. And I mean dam."
"我盖了一个水坝哦"
"As in, I built one."
你就算不好笑也无所谓
And you don't even have to be funny because
贾斯汀·逼勃就已经够好笑了
Justin Beaver does the work for you.
你也来一次 麦克斯
Show him, Max.
"我是直男"
"I'm straight".
你不笑不行啊
You gotta laugh!
是咩
Do I?
真的该笑吗
I mean, honestly?
取笑他的性向吗
Making fun of Justin Beaver's sexuality?
这过火了吧
I find that a tad offensive.
下一段演出 由来自汽车之城的表演者
This next act comes to us from the Motor city.
大家请掌声欢迎 笑星达叔
Please give it up for Mr. Darius the hilarious.
台下的观众今晚好吗
All right. How's everybody doing tonight?
台下的观众有人开斯玛特吗
Who out there has a smart car?
开"半台车"在街上溜达 车主肯定不聪明
Because I don't think it's smart to drive a half a car.
这不笑不行啊
You gotta laugh.
惨了 我逼真的假笑用完了
Oh, no. I ran out of fake laughter.
拜托哦 斯玛特
Yeah, I mean, smart car.
你们看过这种车吗
Have you seen this thing?
这车就像个背包一样的大小
It's like you driving around in a backpack.
这不笑不行啊
You gotta laugh.
是咩
Do we?
你叫斯玛特帮你编段子可能还好笑些
Why don't we have a smart car write some jokes for you?
你替斯玛特辩护我也能理解啦
Yeah, well, I can see why you would defend the smart car.
只有这种车你的小短腿才够得着踏板
It's the only car your feet can reach the pedals in.
说得好对啊 他真的很矮
Yeah, but that's so true. He's very short!
车也矮小 非常合理啊
As is the car. It all lines up.
大家快看这个灰发老鬼
Look at this gray-haired scrub, man.
原来黑人还会显老
Apparently black do crack.
唐金都打电话来了
Hey, Don Kng called.
叫你把他的头还给他
Said he want his whole head back.
麦克斯 你看 厄尔好以儿为傲
Max, look. Look how proud Earl is.
喂喂 金发妞
Hey, hey, hey, blondie.
能等我表演完了再说话吗
You mind not talking until I finish?
等等 估计你脑子里也只在想着
Wait, a minute. You're probably just thinking,
"我的老天 美鞋 美鞋 梳子 美鞋"
"Oh, my god. Shoes, shoes, hairbrush, shoes."
我的老天啊
Oh, my God.
我刚的确是在想美鞋呢
I actually was thinking about shoes!
抱歉 您的卡有点问题
I'm sorry, there's a problem with your card.
显示支付失败
It's been declined.
麦克斯
Max.
小达跟我说了你们的做的事 太有心了
Darius told me what you did and that was awful nice of you.
给 我要还你那些
Now, here. I am reimbursing you
衣服以及那个白痴玩偶的钱
for all of the clothes and for that damn puppet.
即使我曾经发过誓 绝不花钱买海狸[逼]
Although I swore I would never pay for beaver.
你觉得他会成功吗 厄尔
Do you think he'll ever make it, Earl?
现在这年头 谁说的准啊
Who's to say nowadays, Max?
美国达人[有才] 真有咩
America's got talent. Do they?
我只知道他是我的孩子 而你特别费心地
All I know is he's my kid, and you went out of your way
努力去帮他
to try and help him.
我想你能以儿为傲嘛
Well, I just wanted you to be proud.
麦克斯 我十分以你为傲
I am, Max. Very proud.
我跟信用卡公司通了电话
I just talked to VISA.
他们可能挺后悔预先核准了我们的卡
I think they were disappointed they had pre-approved us.
我剪卡了 不剪不行啊
Look, I killed it. I had to.
它在引诱我去买台哈雷摩托车
It was telling me to buy a Harley.
开诚布公地说
Okay, open dialogue.
我昨天用信用卡又买了件东西
I used the credit card for one more thing yesterday.
开诚布公地说 我也是
Open dialogue. So did I.
这是平价商店里 最好的口红了
It's the fanciest lipstick Payless had.
给
And here.
麦克斯 袋子里不会是蜥蜴吧
Max, are there lizards in that bag?
我倒希望
I wish.
跟新的一样 还没有蝴蝶结
They're as good as new and no bows.
麦克斯 你上哪找的补鞋匠
Max, where'd you find a cobbler?
这年头哪有补鞋匠
A cobbler?
我是坐了时光机回过去
I took a time machine.
本该去宰了希特勒的
I was supposed to kill Hitler,
但想到你的鞋子更重要就没去了
but I thought your shoes were more important.
来 剪了你的卡吧
Okay, let's cut up your card.
还是得留着一张 以防生意急需吧
We should keep one for business emergencies.
放到一个我们永远也不会
We just have to have to put it someplace where
想去碰的地方就行了
we'll never be tempted to reach for it.
奥列格 能把这个收你裤裆里吗
Oleg, would you put this down your pants?
没问题
No problem.